people make it very clear that mental health issues are only okay if a white person has them
or someone who is not poor has them when we see like a white man go on a shooting spree and they
want to cite mental health issues oh he was unwell he was this he was that that's like a reason for
us to be understanding of his behavior but if it's a black person and they're mentally ill
and they're yelling on the subway which by the way when you live in new york city there's people
yelling on the subway all the time but if you're a black person and you suffer from mental illness
then you deserve to die just wanted to add an important note for my white followers who have
been responding to the last two story slides and for all in general i hope that you are also having
conversations with your white friends and family about what happened to jordan neely and how it's
being framed in the media i hope that you're also sharing on your social channels what happened to
jordan neely i don't care how many followers you have been through this before i don't care how many
followers you have because we all belong to communities we all have influence in our social
circles so i don't need the shock and awe in my dms what i need is for you to be having conversations
with the people around you about the fact that what happened to jordan neely was wrong
you about that